# ANGELLARREAL

DEVELOPER

Maracaibo, Venezuela +58412-6629930 angellarreal95@gmail.com

#### PROFILE SUMMARY

A Fast Learning Developer with more than 5 years of esperience working as web app developer and mobile developer, Highly skilled in Javascript Frameworks and libraries, 4+ years working with Angular, React and Vue, 2+ Years working with mobile developer tools and frameworks like ionic and Flutter, I really like to learn new technologies and apply them on my work and personal projects

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

### ADITIONAL SKILLS

Angular - 4 years React - 2 years Flutter - 1.5 years

Vue - 1 year

Node - 2 years

NestJS Express Ionic Php Gcp

MySQL MongoDB Firebase Auth0 Javascript **Typescript** 

#### EDUCATION

## **Bachelor of Electronic Engineering,**

**URBE**, Rafael Belloso University

**Bacherlor in Computer Science (5th Semester)** 

University of Zulia

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**Lead Developer** 2022 - today

#### Quik, Venezuela

- Lead Developer in the 2 main apps, created with flutter, in charge of the main features, creation of new interfaces, creation of Quik Go (ridesharing functionality), improvement in the state management of the app, code review, verification of the Pull request of the other developers, mentoring and deploying to the stores.
- Review requirements for new features with the project owner, and stimate time.
- Check the commits and the pull requests from the Flutter/Angular team.
- Create new backend functionality in Firebase Cloud functions with node/express.
- Review old algorithms and methods to make them more proficents and efficients.

**External Works** 2019 - 2022

#### **Upwork-Personal Contact**

- DevWise: creation of templates for five websites using Javasctipt, html, css.
- Creation of two apps for medical appointments, in Ionic with Angular
- Creation of marketing marketing agency in the india, using Javascript, html, css, jaquery, nodeJs, express and php
- RoboComposer, new features on the main App created in react, creation of the translations system for the webpage, and modulation of the page for better perfomance and development using vanilla Javascript.

2016

Mobile Developer 2021 – 2022

#### **Boitas, Mexico**

- Rider app, where the delivery will be tracked and complete the flow with some steps.
- Web view with external authenticaion in Oauth
- Integration of the app with the backend created in GraphQL
- small changes in the webApp

# Full Stack Developer 2021

#### DLDS, Chile

- Implement new features in the main app in Angular, create new modules, and also integrate it with the backend, implement new graphic libraries for the frontend
- Create new methods on the backend with nestJs using node, mysql and mongo, also create integrations with external APIs.

Full Stack Developer 2020-2021

## Linnkr, USA

- Implement new features on the main app in Angular, using rxJS for the conections between the components, implementation of services, api's and pipes.
- Create and Connect to new API services with nodeJs, and nestJS.

## Front-end Developer 2018-2020

#### Intelenz, Venezuela

- Implement new features on the Angular main app, with rxJS.
- Connect to new API, and also create new features with the new data or backend interactions, like dashboards, forms, visual changes.
- Implement new designs, and also develop the new features in Angular